Day 29
1st biker fromiro's workshop,
officially Vinícius.
Thanks. Saw bro?
Ah,
lie.
How are you, okay, brother?
I slept in the gutter,
where I had a flash
but from the troops.
I need a temporary Passenger,
I'm still doing the prospecting,
man,
if it will work,
I don't know,
but I'm doing the prospecting to make a deal huge,
man.
Italy winter here.
Center plus 1 Passenger workshop point.
You can come here to have your little coffee and enjoy theiro workshop.
My brother was also worth it here.
Thanks, Dude,
we're with you.
Oh man,
it's so fucking bro,
that's it
Mano everything is working out,
there are 2 bikers making deliveries,
but I have to give you 1 piece of news.
Tomorrow is the last day of chevas.
The contract I made with the owner was
until tomorrow when he will need the car.
Honestly,
I don't know how I'm going to do it without the chevas.
Oh,
you have a special feeling for him,
are you connected?
I'd rather be grateful for the time I've had with him
than have that running feeling of he's going to leave.
Hand
darkening.
And I'm still here at deliveries,
Man,
an evening delivery.
Here's Samuel and then,
man,
come fix your day,
how's that?
It's two for you,
two, two.
Dude,
knock it,
boom, dude,
want to give me a hug?
I made a drawing for you.
Here is a designer.
Yes,
I was ending now.
.
Look here at the logo from the Brigadier's workshop.
Give a hug here,
bro.
Thanks too much.
See?
I loved it.
It's priceless,
brother,
priceless.
You know,
I'm even excited here.
Oh,
tomorrow.
Last day of the series worth AND that I will miss the glue.